《边桥谜案》前情提要
Previously on The Bridge..
很多事都变了
A lot of things changed.
阿尔玛走了  我的几个女儿也走了
Alma's gone, my daughters are gone,
格斯也死了
Gus is dead.
我理解你的心情
I know what you're thinking.
你想宰了戴维·泰特
You want to kill David Tate.
他夺走了我的一切
He took everything from me.
克罗斯警探
Detective Cross?
我的新娘不见了
My bride is missing.
我在找一个最后出现在华瑞兹的失踪女孩
I'm looking for a missing girl, last seen in Juarez.
那当然
Of course.
你们找的那个女孩  伊娃
我看到她在警察局
一个警察把她带走了
她在哪
我不知道你在说什么
你把那家伙打了一顿
You beat that man up.
他是警察
He was a cop.
你是警察  不能这样做
You're a cop. You can't do that.
但我们找到伊娃了
We found Eva, right?
她被带去了一个派对  下药  强奸
She was taken to a party, drugged, raped.
我们得揭发他们
We need to fix this.
女士
Hey, lady!
一个老人
Some old lady dies
守着巨款去世啊
babysitting a cartel fortune.
不仅如此  还有一半是欧元
That's not all. Half of it's euros.
这是给你的
This came for you.
那是什么
What the hell's that?
钱给你了
米莉·昆塔纳是谁
"米莉·昆塔纳是谁"
"Who is Millie Quintana?"
埃琳娜给我打电话了
丹妮拉出事了
她没下公共汽车
妈妈
Mama...
那些是谁画的
Who did those drawings?
吉姆·多布斯
Jim Dobbs.
看起来像是孩子画的
It looks like they were made by a child.
他杀了我姐姐
He killed my sister.
杀你儿子的那个畜生吗
只要你说话  我马上去办  马可
我会为你宰了他
我想亲手宰了他
建造属于你的山脊
海量供选
请致电奇普·迪亚兹
人人影视
YYeTs.com
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：冰蓝  圈圈  胖兔纯  章鱼  木浅薰  爱卿遛小鸟
■
翻译：foolyangyang  小肚腩  屯栗子  Isabelle  Wdjmhs  潇湘月影
校对：wdjmhs     轴轴：阿包  kitty  安妮
好啊  奇普
Howdy, Chip.
后期：8T     总监：wdjmhs
边桥谜案
第二季第一集
抱歉
Sorry.
桑娅·克罗斯
Sonya Cross.
我马上来
I'll be right there.
趴下  趴在地上
住手  快
住手  这是命令
你在干什么
是我  蠢货  你在干什么
他去了哪里
那个混蛋去了哪里
在那间房里的人  去哪里了
一切都还好吧  老大
你找到毒品了吗  先生
不  什么也没有
阿韦拉多
Abelardo?
你好吗
Como estas?
阿韦拉多  这是乔·麦肯齐和里瓦斯探员
Abelardo, this is Joe McKenzie and Agent Rivas.
他们是缉毒局的人
They're with the DEA.
平塔多先生是我们最厉害的检察官
Senor Pintado is one of our finest prosecutors.
幸会
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
我继续谈备忘录中概述的
I want to get back to the Condor surveillance program
神鹰监督计划
outlined in my memo.
我还没看过你的备忘录
I haven't read your memo yet.
你来总结一下吧
Why don't you summarize?
首先  我们要恭喜
Firstly, we'd like to congratulate
墨西哥新成立的民选政府
the new democratically elected government of Mexico.
同时也恭喜你升职  吉列尔莫
And that goes for your promotion, too, Guillermo.
非常感谢
Muchas gracias.
缉毒局已做好准备  在政府允许的范围内
Now, the DEA stand ready to help in any way
从各方面对你方予以协助
that the administration will allow.
但在我方全部探员被遣返的情况下
We're just not clear how we're supposed to do that
我们不知道该如何开展合作
when all of our agents keep getting sent back home.
神鹰计划是...
Now, what Condor proposes...
你们的心意我们领了  乔
We understand your concern, Joe,
但是我们想用其他方法
but we prefer a different approach
维持好社会秩序
to achieve peace on the streets.
除了跟贩毒集团休战
Short of calling a truce with the cartels
或者是加派人手
or putting more boots on the ground,
我不知道你们还能怎么做
I don't know how you're going to do that.
-任人唯贤  -是
- With competent men in the right positions. - Okay.
就像阿韦拉多这样的人
Men like Abelardo here.
他是奇瓦瓦州新上任的检察官
He's our newly appointed prosecutor to the State of Chihuahua.
-长官  -我正在跟我们的美国朋友
- Sir... - Now, I was just explaining our strategy
解释针对华瑞兹市的策略
in Juárez to our American friends here.
这项政策包括除掉福斯托·加尔文吗
Does this strategy include taking out Fausto Galvan?
打击有组织犯罪  我们得先处理好自己的事
To fight organized crime, we need to clean our own house first.
吉列尔莫  这件事
Guillermo, we have $10 million
我们用了三年  花费了一千万美金
and three years invested in this.
你想就这么完了吗
Are you pulling the plug?
我可没这么说
I didn't say that.
如果你有情报想跟我们分享
If you have any intel you want to share,
我愿意看看
I'm willing to look at it.
你这话什么意思
What exactly does that mean?
不要找我们
Don't call us.
我们会找你们的
We'll call you.
马不错
Nice horse.
你外套上的
On your jacket.
这件外套不是我的
It's not my jacket.
不管是谁的  反正现在穿的人是你
Well, whoever's jacket it is, you're wearing it.
我是杰克·多布斯
I'm Jack Dobbs.
你是来探视的吗
Uh, so, you here to see someone?
对
Yes.
探视你哥哥
Your brother.
我是桑娅·克罗斯  丽莎的妹妹
I'm Sonya Cross, Lisa's sister.
这样啊...
Okay, well...
这里不能抽烟
You can't smoke in here.
是啊
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
你真的是她妹妹吗
You're really her sister?
你跟医生谈过吗
Have you spoken to the doctors?
没有  就问过一个护士
Uh, no, just, just a nurse.
他快不行了
He, uh, he's on the way out.
这可说不准
You don't know that.
我比较了解这些医生
I've been around enough doctors to know.
他们虽然不这么说
I mean, they weren't saying it,
但是一般都这样  你懂的
but they were, if you know what I mean.
那我能做点什么吗
Well, is there something I can do?
比如再找个医生什么的
Like, uh... find a new doctor or...?
你为什么要这样做
Well... Why would you do that?
我不想他死
I don't want him to die.
好吧
Okay.
你想他死吗
Do you want him to die?
我不知道
I don't really know.
我去把烟抽了
Uh, I'm gonna smoke this.
很高兴见到你
Uh, nice to meet you.
欢迎来到美国
请出示护照
Passport?
你来美国做什么
What do you plan to do in the U.S.?
工作
Work.
身上有携带超过一万美元的现金吗
Do you have more than $10,000 on your person?
我带了126美元
I have $126.
好的
Okay.
美国前往墨西哥华瑞兹市
请出示护照
祝你愉快
Have a nice day.
怎么了
What?
说好让你别跟我排一条队的
You were supposed to use a different line.
别紧张  我们过来了
Calm down. We're here.
你应该排另一条队的
You should've used a different line.
为什么不照我说的做
Why didn't you use a different line?
你这排人少
Your line was shorter.
我们是有规矩的
We have a system.
下次别跟我排一条队
Use a different line next time.
我要的越野车呢
Where's the SUV?
这是混合动力汽车
Hybrid.
绿色环保
It's good for the environment.
混合动力
"Hybrid"?
就是油电混合汽车
Electric car.
我担心北极熊会无家可归
I'm worried about the polar bears.
我才懒得管他妈的北极熊
Well, I don't give a shit about polar bears.
我不想看起来像个小受
I don't want to look like a pillow biter.
小受  我不明白
"Pillow biter"? I-I don't understand.
就是同性恋  我不想被当成同性恋  埃利诺
Gay. I don't want to look gay, Eleanor.
但你不是
But you're not gay.
很多美国人都开混合动力汽车
Many Americans drive hybrids.
也有很多美国人是同性恋
And many Americans are gay.
奇瓦瓦州警察局
你还好吗  马可
军火库
还有毒品
那房子里什么都没有
那是你没仔细找
这种小混混长大后就会成为杀手  人贩子
那为什么不把他们都抓了
你不该在这里  马可
别让这帮废物的朋友找机会报复你
走吧
我还要做什么
What should I do with him?
带它回马厩  给它喂点吃的
Take him up to the barn, give him some grain.
好的
Okay.
谢了  伊娃
Thanks, Eva.
什么样的人才会破坏别人的栅栏
What kind of person cuts another man's fence?
这些人总想不劳而获  偷拖拉机  工具
They're looking to steal something-- tractor, tools...
现在还偷起牛来了
stealing cattle now.
伊娃最近怎么样
How's Eva?
好起来
Better.
又变回老样子
Then same.
时好时坏  有时很久都不说一句话
Then better, and some days she don't talk at all.
她有提起过自己的经历吗
She ever talk about what happened?
当她准备好了自然会说
She will when she's ready.
你跟马可联系过吗
You talk to Marco?
他不回我电话
He's not returning my calls.
可能他还需要点时间休整吧
Yeah, I suppose he's still sorting it out.
这样也情有可原
Figure he got his reasons for keeping quiet.
你就是因为这个来找我吗  桑娅
Is that why you come up here, Sonya?
多布斯快死了
Dobbs is dying.
杀死你姐姐的人早就已经死了
The man that killed you sister left this planet a long time ago.
我遇见他弟弟了
I met his brother.
你最好离那家人远点  桑娅
Be best if you steered clear of that entire family, Sonya.
汉克
Hank!
伊娃
Eva?
进去看看
Go in there.
伊娃
Eva?
Eva!
怎么了
What's going on?
发生什么了
What happened?
你还好吗
You all right?
你怎么了
What happened?
先带她回房间里
Take her into the house.
咱们走
Come on, let's go.
先回屋里去
Let's go inside.
怎么了
What happened?
谷仓那边有个人
There was a man in the barn.
她还好吗
Is she all right?
她没事
Yeah.
她告诉你什么了吗
She tell you anything?
她说她认识那人
Said she recognized him.
是华瑞兹那边的警察
Police from Juarez.
该死
Shit.
"米莉·昆塔纳是谁"
谁啊
Who is it?
是我  加里
Uh, it's, uh, Gary.
今天的互助会你没去啊
Missed you at the meeting today.
走开
Go away.
抱歉  我不能不管
Yeah, I can't do that.
怎么不能  赶紧跳回你那
Sure, you can. Just back in that shit-box
垃圾日本车里
Honda of yours and go get a
去吃顿快餐什么的
Happy Meal or something.
你干什么呢
What are you doing?
等电话
Waiting for a call.
看上去挺重要啊
Looks important.
现在不重要  希望过不多久就能派上用场
It's nothing now, but hopefully it will be very soon.
你有一阵子不去互助会了
You haven't been to a meeting in a while.
作为你的担保人  我有责任过来看看
As your sponsor, it's my responsibility to reach out,
看你过得怎么样
see how you're doing.
我挺好
I'm fine.
那你怎么不去参加互助会
Then why haven't you been coming to meetings?
你听费利佩讲他喝得昏天黑地
How many times have you heard Felipe's story about
翻了车死了儿子的故事有多少遍了
getting shit-housed, rolling his car and killing Felipe Jr.?
-很多遍  -还有塔米维柯丁成瘾
- A lot. - Or Tammy getting looped up on Vicodin
跟飞车党混在一起
and passed around that biker gang and liking it?
你这是在转移话题  丹尼尔
Yeah, okay, you're deflecting, Daniel.
我才没有  我只是不需要去参加了
I'm not deflecting. I just don't need it anymore.
我都快无聊死了
It's bumming me out.
你上次喝酒是什么时候
When was the last time you had a drink?
五分钟之前吧
Like five minutes ago.
你坚持了53天都白费了吗
What about your 53 days?
其实只有40天
It's more like 40.
我把事实夸大了一点点
I might've been stretching the truth a little.
再说了  我有自己的方法
Besides, I've got a system.
不  那方法不行
No, systems don't work.
明白吗  相信我
Okay? Trust me.
所有办法我都见识过
I've seen them all.
这回就管用
This one does.
激流乐队  真的假的
Rush? Really?
喝或者不喝选一个
You either drink or you don't.
而且我就是喜欢激流乐队  怎么了
And yeah, I like Rush, so what?
你是加拿大人吗
Are you Canadian?
不是  只是喜欢
No, I'm just a fan.
不醉的时候也喜欢吗
And you like them when you're sober?
只是因为  我是说很好
Because that, I mean, that, I mean, that's impressive.
《2112》是个好专辑
I mean, 2112's an okay album,
但是T恤夸张了点吧
but a T-shirt...?
还有《半球》呢  哥们
Hemispheres, dude?
《半球》简直是...
Hemispheres was like,
-好吧  确实不错  -好吧
- okay, it's fine... - Okay!
你的方式是什么
What is your system?
好的  准备好
Oh, good, ready?
一天两瓶啤酒
Two beers a day.
伏特加呢
What about vodka?
不好  喝伏特加必须配各种药片
No, no! Vodka leads to pills and pills
绝对不是好选择
are not good for Mr. Happy pants.
就一天两瓶啤酒
It's two beers a day.
也给我留点希望
It gives me something to look forward to.
一天两瓶啤酒
Yeah, two beers a day
绝对不可能  因为你有酒瘾  丹尼尔
is not gonna work 'cause you're an addict, Daniel.
我现在是有点醉  明天我就清醒了
I may be buzzed now,but tomorrow I'll be sober,
而你  还是激流的粉丝
and you, sir, will still be a Rush fan.
真幽默
Yeah, funny.
今晚有个见面会
There's a meeting tonight.
来电话了  好吗
That's my phone. Okay.
我得接一下
I gotta take this.
我是弗莱
Hey, this is Frye.
收杯酒
请进
你在外面多久了
How long were you out there?
就一会儿
Not long.
就看着我吗
Watching me?
是
Yes.
现在你离了婚
Well, at least you can have sex
至少可以和别的女人上床了吧
with other women now that you're divorced, huh?
你这是想开玩笑吗
That supposed to be a joke?
不是
No.
阿尔玛不愿意让我看自己的孩子出生
Alma doesn't want me at the birth of my own child.
很遗憾
I'm sorry.
桑娅  如果你是想看看我
Look, Sonya, if you came by to check on me,
我很好
I'm-I'm fine.
有人跟踪伊娃
A man came after Eva.
她人呢
Where was she?
汉克家
Hank's.
她认出了跟踪者
She recognized him.
是谁
Yeah?
一个警察
A cop.
华瑞兹市的
From Juarez.
你确定吗
Destas segura?
我确定  马克
Yes, I'm sure, Marco.
她吓坏了  她认识他
She was terrified. She knew him.
这里到底怎么回事
What's going on down here?
他们知道我们救了她
They know we saved her.
她本来应该死掉了的
She wasn't supposed to be saved.
昨天  有人想要杀我
Yesterday, someone tried to kill me.
我们被袭击了
We were on a raid.
我一转身  他就站在那
I turn, and there he was.
我们当时带着面具  而且天色很暗
We were wearing masks and it was dark,
所以没看到他的脸  但是
so I couldn't see who he was, but..
我确定那是我们自己人
it was one of my own men.
我们怎么办
What are we gonna do?
我们
We?
这是我自己的麻烦
This is my problem.
我会处理的
I'll deal with it.
不好意思  这跟你又有什么关系
I'm sorry, how is this your problem?
我赌上工作把一个非法移民
I risked my job smuggling an illegal immigrant
-偷运到美国境内  -不不不
- into the united States. - Ah, ch... No, no, no,
是无正式文件的  不是非法
undocumented-- not illegal.
他们去汉克家找她了
They showed up at Hank's house looking for her.
你还不明白吗
Can't you get it?
如果他们要我死  我就死定了
If they want me dead, they can make it happen.
随时  就像这样
At any time, like that.
你也是
Same for you.
我跟你说  马可
You know what, Marco?
你准备好做事后再给我电话吧
Why don't you call me when you're ready to do something?
有什么事吗
我叫阿韦拉多·平塔多
是奇瓦瓦州的检察官
我找罗伯斯队长
他不在
他让你这么说的  是吧
没关系  我很有耐心
丽莎·克罗斯
德州埃尔帕索警局
他怎么样
How is he?
我不知道  他们
Uh, well, I don't know.They, uh,
带他去医院做核磁共振还有其它检查了
took him to the hospital for an MRI and some other tests.
那很好
Well, that's good.
也许吧
Maybe.
有什么消息我可以通知你
I can call you if there's news.
如果你想知道的话
That's if you want to know.
我想
I do.
那天的事很抱歉
And, uh, I'm sorry about the other day.
正如我所说  这
Like I said, this...
这整件事都有点
this whole thing is kind of...
怪怪的
Yeah, weird.
你说的就是"怪怪的"
Weird is-is-is what you said.
是啊  算是吧
Yeah, no, kind of.
我们能谈谈吗
Could we talk?
好
Yeah.
我有很多
I-I just have a lot of...
很多问题
a lot of questions.
关于你哥哥的
About your brother.
好  附近有餐厅
Yeah, okay, uh, there's food here.
好  很好
Okay, yeah, that's perfect.
行
Okay.
要我陪你进去吗
You want me to come in with you?
要  把你的工具带上
Yes. Bring your tools.
带着呢
I got 'em.
你们好
Hi. How are you?
欢迎来到雷伯恩国民银行
Welcome to Rayburn National Bank.
德拉格先生在办公室等着了
Uh, Mr. Delarge is waiting in his office,
请你们跟我来
if you'd like to follow me, please.
需要什么喝的吗
Uh, can I get you anything to drink?
一杯茶  加蜂蜜和奶油
I would like some tea with honey and cream.
好  这位先生呢
Okay, yeah, uh, sir?
不要吗  好的  这边请
No? Okay, uh, right this way, please.
什么事
Yes?
德拉格先生  您的客户到了
Uh, hi, Mr. Delarge. Your clients are here.
这边请
Right this...
谈话愉快
Have a great meeting.
纳赫特女士
Ms. Nacht.
真有这个必要吗
Is that really necessary?
手机
Phone.
拜托了
Please.
知道我们为什么在这儿吗
You know why we're here?
那是...
That's a...
米奇·曼托签过名的棒球
a signed Mickey Mantle ball.
他是什么人
And who's that?
尤凡尼  把球放回去
Yovani, please return the ball.
它不是你的
It doesn't belong to you.
多谢
Thank you.
这金发小妞儿多大
How old is the blonde?
什么
What?
你女儿
Your daughter.
她多大
How old is she?
她的眼睛真漂亮
She has nice eyes.
我想知道昆塔纳家发生了什么事
I want to know what happened at the Quintana house.
挺反常的
It was a freak thing.
她中风了
She had a stroke.
钱不应该在那
The money wasn't supposed to be there.
就像我跟你说的那样  我们耽搁了
Well, like I told you, we had a delay.
我们原本以为
We understood you,
你们能处理好那些钱
uh, would be able to handle the volume.
是的  我们能
And we can.
那为什么没做到
Then why didn't you?
不会再有下次了
That will not happen again.
但这次犯了错
But it did.
是的  我们失误了
Yes, it did,
但我已经做好了善后工作
and I have made the necessary corrections.
这次我们损失了6042.7万美元
Leaving us with a negative balance of $60,427,000.
其中还包括按照当前汇率换算的欧元
That includes the euros at the current exchange rate.
为什么钱没有搬到应该放置的地方
Why wasn't the money moved when it was supposed to?
详细解释给我听
Explain that to me exactly.
我的寄件员搞混了收件日期
My courier confused the pickup dates.
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
但就像我说的  我  我已经...
But, like I said, i've-I've...
我已经处置他了
I've dealt with him.
如何处置的
Dealt with him how?
请把他的名字告诉我
I need a name, please.
我的职责就是对事件进行详述记录
It is my job to provide thorough accounting of how it happened.
他还有家室
He has a family.
-是吗  那又怎样  -求你了
- Yes. So?  - Please.
这杯是放了蜂蜜和奶油的茶
Uh, uh, tea with honey and cream.
天哪
Oh, my gosh.
我  太对不起了  我...
I... I'm so sorry, I...
别碰我
Don't touch me.
尤凡尼
Yovani.
太对不起了  德拉格先生  我...
I'm so sorry, Mr. Delarge, I'm...
都是我不好  太对不起了  我...
It's my f... So sorry, I...
等等  等等  你要干什么...
Wait, wait, what are you do...
等一下
Hey, wait a minute.
你要干什么
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
割手指
手
还是耳朵
割耳朵
闭上嘴  混蛋
天哪
Oh, God.
你不会报警或者告诉别人吧
You won't call the police or tell anybody what happened.
不会
No.
你也有家室  不是吗  德拉格先生
You have a family, too. Don't you, Mr. Delarge?
现在请把寄件员的名字告诉我
Now I need the name of the courier... please.
你不像个警察
You don't look like a cop.
那也挺好
And that's a good thing,
因为通常我不喜欢和警察交谈
'cause usually I don't like talking to cops.
为什么  你犯罪了吗
Why? Are you a criminal?
没有
No.
现在没有
Not right now.
逗你玩的
That's a joke.
我找到笑点了
No, I get it, I get it.
特别好笑
That's hilarious.
好了
Okay.
我懂了
I get it.
你想了解我哥哥的事
You want to know about my brother.
我想知道他为什么要杀我姐姐
I want to know why he picked my sister.
我们都想知道他为什么这么对你姐姐
We all drove ourselves crazy asking why he did that to your sister.
审判之后
After the trial, my,
我...我爸自杀了
uh... my old man killed himself.
用的猎枪
Shotgun.
我妈几年后也去世了
My mother passed a couple years later.
得了癌症
Cancer.
我觉得这都是因果联系的
I think it's... it's all related, you know.
就像是吉米做了那事之后的报应
Like some kind of karma for what Jimmy did.
我不相信因果报应
I don't believe in karma.
为什么
Why not?
世事无常
Things just happen.
但这总是冥冥中有安排
But there's a pattern out there,
比如我们的见面
like... like us meeting.
没有什么安排
There's no pattern.
你哥哥杀了我姐姐
Your brother killed my sister.
那你想要我说什么
Well, what do you want me to say?
对不起
I'm sorry.
那一天
And that day...
那一天毁了我的一生
That day messed up my entire life
我想也毁了你们家庭吧
and I'm guessing it did a number on your family.
感谢你请我吃午餐
Thanks for lunch.
不用谢
You're welcome.
等等
Uh, wait...
我有东西要给你看
There's something I want to show you.
丹尼尔·弗莱
Daniel Frye.
一直
Never, uh...
一直不知道你叫什么
Never caught your name.
随便你怎么叫吧
Whatever you want it to be.
好的
OK.
那就叫你
How about, uh...
那就叫你混球
How about Dick?
可以
That works.
你有五分钟
You got five minutes.
好的  那...
All right, so...
放回去
Put that away.
这个不准记
This is off the record.
机密啊  好的
Deep cover. You got it.
那你有什么情报  混球
So, what you got, Dick?
局长正在考虑你的信息自由申请
My department chief is sitting on your FOIA request.
真的假的
No shit.
昆塔纳  昆塔纳  昆塔纳
Quintana, Quintana, Quintana.
同一天给予庇护
All given asylum on the same day.
看到日期了吗
You see the date?
谁能这么安排
Who could order something like this?
我这个级别肯定不行
Way above my pay grade.
一定有人受贿了  对吧
Somebody's got to be on the take, right? I mean...
听着  我不会回答这种问题
Listen, I don't answer questions like that.
你什么都没看到  我们没见过面
Look, you never saw this, and we never met.
你不知道掌权的社会党人会对我这种
Don't you know what the socialists in power would do to
9级公务员做什么吗
a GS-9 like me?
我不知道  混球
I don't know, Dick.
那些掌权的社会党人会怎么做
What would the Socialists in power do?
取消你五周带薪休假
Take away your five weeks paid vacation?
就是这个
This is it.
照片里是你  对不对
That's you, isn't it?
嗯  是的
Mmm, yeah.
你从哪得到的
Where did you get this?
他被捕时身上带着的
He had it on him when he was arrested.
你是说他被枪击那天
You mean shot.
对
Yeah.
我记得这天
I remember this day.
天气很好
It was a good day.
这个能给我吗
Can I have this?
当然可以
Sure.
没问题
Yeah, of course.
谢谢
Thanks.
我
I, uh...
我该走了
I should go.
我不想让你走
I don't want you to go.
好吧
Okay.
你在
What are you...?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
前戏
Foreplay?
是吗
Yeah?
很奇怪吗
Is this weird?
对
Yeah.
很棒
或许你该走了
Maybe you should go.
我走不了
I can't.
她是你妈妈
She's your mother.
我是说  那人看到她怎么办
I mean, what if this guy saw her?
他没看到
No, he didn't.
我妈妈悬赏想获得达尼的消息
My mother put up a reward for information about Dani.
她还存着希望
She still has hope.
那些打电话的人就是想要钱
These people who are calling just want the money.
达尼没有失踪
Dani's not lost.
她没有逃跑
She didn't run away.
她死了
She's dead.
你没法确定
You don't know that.
我不想再说了  可以吗
I just don't want to talk about this anymore, okay?
老兄  我一直在找你
Dude... dude, I've been looking for you.
凯利说你
Kelly said you...
凯利说你在吃午饭
Kelly said you were just having lunch.
没关系
It's okay.
只是午餐而已
It is just lunch.
那个
That...
你是
Are-are you, uh...?
露西
Lucy.
你肯定是丹尼尔了
You must be Daniel.
是我
That's me--
那个混球
the dickhead.
她的确提过这个
Ah, she did mention something about that.
什么
What?
坐吧
Grab a chair.
好
Yeah.
你吃完了吗
Oh, are you done?
因为我有点饿了
Because I am, like, starving.
没关系  都给你吃
No, it's all yours.
多谢
Thank you so much.
天呐  你可真美
My God, you are pretty.
你的双唇  太完美了
You've got, like, perfect lips.
真给力啊
That's awesome.
你喝酒了吗
Have you been drinking?
就两瓶啤酒  没事
Two beers. I'm fine.
跟你公开一下
Full disclosure,
本混球我还是个精神正常的酒鬼
this dickhead is also a fully-functioning alcoholic.
丹尼尔  你找我什么事
Daniel, what do you want?
我见了我的线人
Oh, um... met with my source.
知道  移民局的那个人
Yeah, your guy in immigration.
对  听着
Yeah, so listen.
钱庄开业前两个月  米莉·昆塔纳的
So, three of Millie Quintana's relatives from Guatemala all got
三个危地马拉亲戚就已经获准在美国避难
asylum six months before that money house went on line.
这么说米莉在移民局里有关系
So Millie has connections in Immigration?
没错  应该是这样
Yeah, right. I mean, it's got to be that, or,
要么就是她的雇主
like, whoever she's working for...
可能谁有这个能耐吧
Someone-someone made that happen.
该死
Shit.
我得走了
I got to go.
本就不该来打扰的
I shouldn't have interrupted.
认识你真的很开心
It was so lovely meeting you.
我也是
Same here.
丹尼尔
Hey, Daniel.
我们要把那些亲戚找出来
We need to find those relatives.
建造属于你的山脊
海量供选
请致电奇普·迪亚兹
我以为你会废他的手
I thought you were gonna go for his hand.
耳朵更好
Ear was better.
他又不听话
He wasn't listening.
若你需要  等解决掉美国佬
You want, we can get you a new dress...
可以给你弄条新裙子来
after we get the Yankee.
我帮你出主意
I could give you my thoughts,
让你看起来体面些
help you look good.
美国人  不加冠词
It is "Yankee," Not "The Yankee,"
我不需要新裙子
And I don't need a new dress.
随你
Whatever.
奇普·迪亚兹
Chip Diaz.
幸会幸会
Nice to meet you.
你好
Hello.
你想从哪里开始
Where would you like to start?
里边
Inside.
太棒了
Fantastic.
如果你喜欢  我还准备了些点心
I've got some refreshments, if you'd like.
带工具吗
Tools?
不用
No.
有问题吗
Something wrong?
走吧
Go on.
马可
队长
你去哪了
法院
恢复自由身了
她都没现身
她的律师签的协议书
这样更好
你得帮我个忙
新来的检察官到了
我看见他了
你懂的  新官上任三把火
他想怎么样
所有的检察官想要的都一样
打响自己的名号
替我照顾好他
给他看人事档案  回答他的问题
好的
你懂的
马可·鲁伊斯
久闻大名
你要看档案  对吗
拜托了
你在边桥上事  我都看过了
对令郎的不幸  我深表哀悼
谢谢
抱歉这里比较乱
不是一直这样的
罗伯斯队长
别担心  你们队长这种人我见多了
没事的  交给我  我能搞定
我能帮你做点什么吗
不用
不过等我安顿下来后  想跟你谈谈
等我屡清头绪以后
我得先请示一下队长
应该的  应该的
你每件事都跟他请示吗
看情况
什么情况
看我是否认为他需要知道
这种态度比较危险
你到底要查什么
还不能确定
查到了才能知道
谢谢
你要喝点什么吗
Would you like something to drink?
不用了
No, I'm good.
谢谢
Thanks.
我貌似应该...
Thinking maybe I should, uh,
走了
get going.
好的
Okay.
这是他送给你的吗
Did he, uh, give you those?
是的
Yeah.
他为我画的
He drew them for me.
你为什么把他们挂起来
Why would you, uh, put them up?
我喜欢看
I like looking at them.
好吧
Okay.
我...
I, uh...
该走了
should get going.
好的
Okay.
再见
Bye.
你确定要这么做吗
Sure you want to do this?
我有别的选择吗
What else am I gonna do?
我在想办法偷偷的给你办个签证
I'm trying to get you a visa without raising too many red flags.
这只是临时情况  好吗
So this will be a temporary situation, okay?
直到我找到别的办法
Until I figure something out.
他们要回到你的住处怎么办
What if they come back to your house?
如果那样
Well, if they do,
他们不会有好果子吃的
they're not gonna like what they find.
对不起
I'm sorry about this.
不  我给你添了这么多麻烦
No. I-I've been too much trouble, I'm...
没有
No, you haven't.
没必要内疚  伊娃
Nothing to be sorry about, Eva.
-我得先跟这家伙说两句话  -好的
- I need to have a word with this guy first, all right? - Okay.
你来晚了
You're late.
该死的流浪狗  我想抓它  结果它逃掉了
Dang stray dog-- I tried to catch it, but it eluded me.
很漂亮的柯利牧羊犬
Dang good-looking collie.
你好  伊娃
Hello, Eva.
你喜欢柯利牧羊犬吗
You like collies?
没什么喜不喜欢
No opinion.
这种狗不错
Well, it's a good breed, generally.
是个好帮手
Helpful.
先把话说清楚
Let's get something straight.
这件事上  我一点执法能力都没有
I'm here in a non-law enforcement capacity, all right?
别担心
Don't worry.
她跟着我会很安全
She'll be safe with me.
而且斯蒂文兄弟很快就回来了
Plus Brother Steven will be back soon.
他俩心有灵犀
They have a spiritual connection.
听着  我不信任你
Look, I don't trust you,
也不信任那个疯子林德
I don't trust that wing nut Linder, neither.
一点都不信
Not as far as I could throw you.
来这里是她的主意
This was her idea to come here.
我查了你的老底  鲍勃
See, I ran your name, Bob.
你要跟我说说塔尔萨那事吗
You want to tell me about what happened in Tulsa?
-哪件事  -驾驶轻型摩托车进行人身伤害
- Which thing? - Felony assault with a dirt bike.
我那是被触犯了底线
Well, it was one of those stand your ground things,
只是当时恰好骑着辆雅马哈
it just happened to be on a Yamaha.
说不定还磕了点冰毒
Might have been some meth involved
你懂的
you know what I'm talking about.
你还在嗑药吗  鲍勃
You still tweakin', Bob?
我洗心革面了
I'm not that man anymore.
你还想知道什么
You have anything else you want to know?
你在牧场做些什么
Yeah, what do you got going on up at that ranch?
代主行事
The Lord's work.
那里是避风港
A safe haven.
天国通路
The Path.
眼下
For the moment...
我姑且让她跟你走
I'm gonna let her go with you, all right?
但你有责任照顾好她
But you're responsible for her.
如果她出了事
If anything happens to her,
你得给我个交待  明白吗
you answer to me, do you understand?
明白
Yeah, I do.
很好
Good.
你好  马可
Hola, Marco.
你眼神很哀伤
今晚我什么都做不了
那要看你今晚怎么过
没事吧
没事  只是睡不着
要一起喝一杯吗
卡车司机报的警
Trucker called it in.
那是条狗吗
Is that a dog?
是的
Yes, it is.
咱们得把车停下
We need to stop it.
是啊  我是想先让你看看
Yeah, I wanted you to see what we're up against first.
这是辆混合动力车  要好久才回自己停下
Course, it's a hybrid, so it ain't like we can wait it out.
头儿
Boss.
这他妈是什么
What the hell is this?
我也想问
Exactly.
女侠出马了
There she goes.
伙计  你看
Dude, look.
那是什么
What is that?
伙计  去看看
Dude, check it out.
帮帮我
Help me.